hello everyone this is ey on ey censored
Supernatural Bible changes on YouTube
and today is the 18th of January
2024 this will be a quick video this is
about a book review my latest book
available on Amazon College Matrix and
looking glasses Supernatural Bible
changes yes looking
glasses is in the Bible and it's one
word how crazy is that we are seeing our
bibles are being
invaded through witchcraft we are now
seeing all types of errors in our Bibles
specifically the King James Bible but
every Bible translation in every
language across the
Earth is supernaturally changing as
crazy as that sounds the changes are
self-evident preparing the way for the
Antichrist and coming with World satanic
system we were warned of this hour in
scripture in 2 Thessalonians 2 and
there's no doubt about it that our
bibles are changing and it's crazy I've
been covering these changes for the past
seven and a half years on YouTube now
this book focuses on all the words
related not all of them but a majority
of words new words in the Bible related
to
education now why is this happening I
believe that changing the words in the
Bible are having impact in the natural
it's Alchemy it's
witchcraft fasting of spells and if we
have eyes to see you'll know that our
whole educational system is compromised
today with demonic
agendas satanic
perversion and it's time to wake up in
Jesus
name now what I've done in this short
little book it's a small book 5.75 by 6
in and I give a little in the beginning
I share what's happening and why and
then I share verse after verse after
verse after verse of changes in
Scripture that should be self-evident to
anyone because you're going to see new
words you're going to see nonsense
verses you're going to read um you're
going to see punctuation errors
doctrinal errors grammar errors new
people new language one verse can have
be a total rewrite
unrecognizable our bibles are being
prepared for the
Antichrist and the Bible told us that
the
Antichrist will pretend that he's God
and there will be a great Falling Away
this is the abomination of desolation
happening right now let me show you what
this book is about this is from
Amazon and I want to tell you that the
Bible now has words like college Matrix
and looking glasses but also Scholars
alter Ed instructors pen paper School
theater Compass science and many other
new words related to education now in
the Bible it's staggering and it's time
to wake up in Jesus name there are many
agendas that are infiltrating
scripture many of them and I've been
covering these on YouTube for the past
seven and a half years and now I have
other books that I've written
covering various agendas that we now see
plopped into the Bible making it very
easy for you to research this out I'm
putting together books I've been
studying this researching this for S and
a half
years and I've been able to categorize
these according to
agendas and now I'm sharing with you
which I've been doing on my YouTube
channel e
censored I pray that these tools will be
of benefit to you as your researching
this
topic as you are sharing with
others that
the obvious attack against scripture
today
supernaturally will be made clear and
apparent to the reader he who readeth
let him
understand the abomination of desolation
is taking place right now while the
church
sleeps Jesus Christ is the word of God
and the word of God endures forever our
bibles are
changing and it's time to wake up in
jesus' name I implore you and I beseech
you to pray and fast and seek the Lord
open up your Bibles do your
research and do not be
deceived that is the whole purpose of
what we're seeing happen today and
woefully many people who call themselves
Christians
deny what's happening when it's so
self-evident and they are clearly
underneath the strong delusion we were
warned
about be strong and courageous brothers
and sisters do not fear or be dismayed
for the Lord your God is with you
wherever you go until next
time